I told y'all before, i'mma tell y'all again.
Get you a AARP card.
We always thought you had to be like 55 or older to get one.
No, all you need to be is 18 years old.
You can get access to the discount the hotels,
the rentals, Outback Steakhouse
at and T phone uses to get $10 off per line per month.
Disney discounts, Universal Studio discounts,
resume help, career classes.
It's so many things. And you can get access to it.
Membership right now is $15 for one year.
You can also add another member completely free.
If you wanna go get you one,
comment AARP and the direct link will send to your DM.
If you don't see it, make sure you check your message request.
And yes,
you can go and get the flyer out the mail or call them yourself.
But I'll put you on so use my link.
You can also go directly to my blog Mama likes to save dot com.
Click freebies and trials.
You'll see the AARP one
as well as a bunch of other things that's free or trial
or discounts on things.
I hope this helps me so you follow me for more tips and deals haha.
And tell a friend!